const geas_subject = {
    1: {
        "question": "What is the short title of RA 9292?",
        "choices": [
            "Electronics Engineering Law of 2004",
            "Electronics and Communications Engineering Law of 2007",
            "Electronics and Communications Engineering Law of 2014",
            "Electronics Engineering Law of 2009",
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Electronics Engineering Law of 2004"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "The science dealing with the development and application of devices and systems involving the flow of electrons or other carriers of electric charge...",
        "choices": [
            "Electronics",
            "Information and Communications Technology",
            "Computers",
            "Communications"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Electronics"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "Any of a variety of electronic devices capable of accepting data, programs, and/or instructions...",
        "choices": [
            "Computers",
            "Information and Communications Technology",
            "Electronics",
            "Communications"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Computers"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "The acquisition, production, transformation, storage, and transmission/reception of data and information by electronic means...",
        "choices": [
            "Communications",
            "Information and Communications Technology",
            "Electronics",
            "Computers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Information and Communications Technology"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "The process of sending and/or receiving information, data, signals, and/or messages between two or more points...",
        "choices": [
            "Information and Communications Technology",
            "Communications",
            "Computers",
            "Electronics"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Communications"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "Any transmission, emission, or reception of voice, data, electronic messages, text, pictures, signals, or other information...",
        "choices": [
            "Communications Engineering",
            "Telecommunications",
            "Broadcasting",
            "Transmission Engineering"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Telecommunications"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "An undertaking to transmit audio, video, text, images, or other signals for a broad audience...",
        "choices": [
            "Telecommunications",
            "Communications Engineering",
            "Broadcasting",
            "Transmission Engineering"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Broadcasting"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "Includes all manufacturing establishments and other business endeavors where electronic or electronically-controlled machinery or equipment are installed...",
        "choices": [
            "Industrial Plant",
            "Industrial Electronics",
            "Electronic Business",
            "Electronic Commerce"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Industrial Plant"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "Include services requiring adequate technical expertise, experience, and professional capability in the field of electronics engineering...",
        "choices": [
            "Designing Services",
            "Signing Services",
            "Consulting Services",
            "Intermediary Services"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Consulting Services"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "What is Section 4 of RA 9292?",
        "choices": [
            "Nature and Scope of Practice",
            "Powers and Functions of the Board",
            "Categories of Practice",
            "Composition of the Board"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Categories of Practice"
    }
};